Guide to the COLLECTION NAME HERE, YYYY-YYYY IBT0084
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Campaigns, Educational videos, Promotions, Rallies, Safety videos and Other Miscellaneous Videos, Series 3
  - Diamond Walnut #1, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Ergonomics/Teamsters/UPS MacNiel/Leher Newhour, PBS- Wash. D.C.February 27,1995, 1995-02-27; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Fair Trade Agreement Q+A continued IBT Legislative COnference, San Francisco May 12,1992- Reel 13 13:00:00, 1992-05-12; Series 3; Betacam (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Filmakers Union Oicket/Dispute IBT, Channel 4, Pittsburgh February 2, 1993 @ noon, 1993-02-02; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - The "Final Offer": Landmines and Timebombs 1993 UAW PR Department, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - A Fine and Long Tradition- "Our History is our Strength" National Women's History Project 1996, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Figurhut Powers Smith Teamsters TV Spot- Ganske- "Mother B" August 31, 1995, 1995-08-31; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - FITZ openings Video Programs, Series 3 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - "Five Days That Shook the Teamsters"Edit: Matt Micka Minnesota T.D.U., Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Five finalists for Bushin Spots moveon.org, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Five Finalists for Bushin Spots (Undated), Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - F.J. Spears Trial December,1995, 1995-12; Series 3; Reel (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Flags for Sale English Version, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Flood Relief Convoy January, 1997, 1997-01-01; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Frank E Fitzsimmons Intro to Teamsters Videotape network, Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - "Freight '98: Fighting for Our Future" 7 min. 1998, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - "Freight '98: Fighting for Our Future" 1998 7 min., Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Glass Shield Public Services/Police, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - G.E. special- Sammy Davis, Jr., Series 3; U-matic (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Glen Pearcy Productions "Teamsters and out communities: Hand-in-Hand" July 11, 1996- Edited Master, 1996-07-11; Series 3; D2 digital (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Glen Pearcy Productions "Teamsters and Our Communities: Hand-in-Hand" July 12, 1996, 1996-07-12; Series 3; Betacam (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Going Up the River, The Long War of John Kerry, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Going Up the River, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters The James R. Hofffa Memorial Scholarship Fund 2001 Year Recipients, Series 3; Betacam (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - "Half a Job is Not Enough" Rallies News Clips, NY Local 804 Interview San Francisco, Rockford, IL, Louisville June 27-29 July 1997, 1997-06-27-1997-06-29; 1997-07; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Hayward Ratification Meeting Pre-Meeting Jan. 27,1985 #16 SF, 1985-01-27; Series 3; U-matic (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Hayward Pre-Ratification Meeting January 27,1985 #17 SF, 1985-01-27; Series 3; U-matic (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - "Hazardous Materials Training" A CFMF Video March, 1995, 1995-03; Series 3; VHS (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - HBO: Hoffa Tape 6 BB+B Rally NY September 12,1999, 1999-09-12; Series 3; Betacam (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - HBO Hoffa Project NTR Rally- IBT Crew April 12,2000, 2000-04-12; Series 3; Betacam (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - HBO Segment: American Standoff June 10, 2002, 2002-06-10; VHS (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - "Health Care Reform: We Can't Afford to Wait" Labor Institute of Public Affairs, Series 3; VHS (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - "Heroes Every Day" AFL-CIO November 28, 2001, 2001-11-28; Series 3; VHS (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - The Hidden Faces of Globalization 2003, Series 3; VHS (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - "Hiring Rosa Martinez"- 60mins CBS- 9/27/92 "Paying to Lose Our Jobs" Nightline ABC- 9/29 and 9/30/92 National Labor Committee Education Fund in Support of Worker and Human Rights in Central America, 1992-09-27; 1992-09-29-1992-09-30; Series 3; VHS (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - "Hiring Rosa Martinez"- 60mins CBS- 9/27/92 "Paying to Lose Our Jobs" Nightline ABC- 9/29 and 9/30/92 National Labor Committee Education Fund in Support of Worker and Human Rights in Central America, 1992-09-27; 1992-09-29-1992-09-30; Series 3; VHS (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - History of Fighting, 2011; Series 3; CD (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Hoffa '96, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Hoffs '96, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Hoffa for Teamster President, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Hoffa Slate/Leedham Slate IBT Teamster Candidate Forum, Series 3; VHS (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - "Teamsters Partnership with Habitat Humanity", 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Partnership with Habitat for Humanity Feb 1996, Series 3; Betacam (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - "Teamsters Partnership with Habitat for Humanity 10min, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Habitat for Humanity Teamster Partnership, Series 3; VHS (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - "Home of the Brave" Documentary, Series 3; VHS (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - House Calls, Organizing Dept. Teamsters Union 24min, Series 3; VHS (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - House Calls 1996, Series 3; VHS (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - This is Habitat for Humanity, Series 3; VHS (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - "Teamsters Partnership with Habitat for Humanity" 1996, Series 3; VHS (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - IBT Nader Campaign News Conference, Series 3; VHS (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - IBT Nader Campaign News Conference, Series 3; VHS (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - IBT Nader Campaign News Conference, Series 3; VHS (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - IBT Nader Campaign News Conference, Series 3; VHS (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - IBT Nader Campaign News Conference, Series 3; VHS (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - IBT Nader Campaign News Conference, Series 3; VHS (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - IBT/NAFTA "Ten Years of Broken Promises" March 23, 2004, 2004-03-23; Series 3; VHS (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - IBT/NAFTA "Ten Years of Broken Promises" Nov. 24, 2003, 2003-11-24; Series 3; VHS (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - IBT/NAFTA "Ten Years of Broken Promises" Nov. 24, 2003, 2003-11-24; Series 3; VHS (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - IBT: "One Strike You're Out!" 15min, Series 3; VHS (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - IBT organizing for Power June 7, 2006, 2006-06-07; Series 3; VHS (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - IBT- Organizing for Power Jun 8, 2006 2:19mins, 2006-06-8; Series 3; Betacam (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - IBT Overnite June 20, 2001 Final Cut, 2001-06-20; Series 3; VHS (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - IBT Education- Skills for Tomorrow, 2001-04-18; Series 3; VHS (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - IBT- Exporting Jobs Nightline ABC, Washington, D.C., 1992-09-30; Series 3; VHS (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - IBT footage from Springfield, MO Window Dub, Tapes 1-3, 2000-11-04; Series 3; VHS (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - IBT International Overnite Campaign "60 Minutes Television, 2000-03; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - IBT International Overnite Campaign :60 Television, 2000-03; Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - IBT/JAB(Joint Association of Boxers) Press Conference+Event, 2003-03-12; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - IBT 1991 Convention June 24,1991 -Monday Tape 2, 1991-06-24; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - IBT Communications Teamsters's/Organizing 2004 "Revolution", Series 3; VHS (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - IBT Marketing Video-loop 4x, 2001-06-21; Series 3; VHS (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - IBT Nightly Business Report, PBS, Wash. D.C. June 17, 1992 Teamsters on Free Trade Policy, 1992-06-17; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - IBT MPLS Rally Tape 1, 2001-02-17; Series 3; Betacam (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - IBT MPLS Rally Tape 2, 2001-02-17; Series 3; Betacam (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - IBT Palmer House Hotel Grand Ballroom Reel #4 4:50-6:15 pm (undated), Series 3; C-slot reel (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - IBT Port Division "Driving it Home", Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - IBT Port Division "Driving It Home", Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - IBT Port Division "Driving It Home", Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - IBT Port Division "Driving It Home", Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - IBT Port Division "Driving It Home" (Final Revision), 2000-03; Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - IBT Port Division "Driving It Home" (Final Revision), 2000-03; Series 3; VHS (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - IBT Port Division "Driving It Home" (Final Revision) 6:45 mins, 2000-03; Series 3; VHS (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - IBT Port Division "Driving It Home" (Final Revision) 6:45 mins, 2000-03; Series 3; VHS (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - IBT Port Division "Making a Livin", 2000-03; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - IBT- Project RISE Video, 2000-09-29; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - IBT Port Division- Loop 7x, 2001-06-21; Series 3; VHS (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - IBT "Rights at Overnite" TV Spot, 2000-03-27; Series 3; VHS (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - IBT Scholarship -Sample-, 2001-06-07; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - IBT Teamsters Caravan Kero TV, Bakersfield, 1994-02-01; Series 3; VHS (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - IBT UPS 2002: "Whatever it Takes", 2002-03-10; Series 3; VHS (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - IBT- Warehouse Walmart: Not as Advertised with Hoffa Intro 9:30 mins, Series 3; VHS (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Identify Opportunities... Expanding Solutions Annual Shareholders' Meeting, 2002-03; Series 3; VHS (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Inside Politics with Dana Bush Teamsters Disaffiliation from the AFL-CIO, 2005-07-25; Series 3; VHS (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - International Council Meeting New York City (Undated), Series 3; Reel to reel (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Introducing the Union Savings and Investment Plan, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - "Iron Jawed Angels" re: Women's Suffrage 2hrs, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - "It's Our Contract: We'll Fight for It!" 4 mins, 1997; Series 3; VHS (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - "It's Our Contract: We'll Fight for it!" 4 mins, 1997; Series 3; VHS (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - JAB/Teamster Affiliation- ESPN, 2003-05-09; Series 3; VHS (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - The James R Hoffa Memorial Scholarship Fund 2001 Recipients, Series 3; VHS (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - The James R Hoffa Memorial Scholarship Fund 2001 year Recipients, 2001-06-18; Series 3; VHS (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Joint Association of Boxers Friday Night Fights ESPN, 2005-03-04; Series 3; VHS (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Julian Michaels aka Michael J Saipaia National Anthem Singer, Series 3; VHS (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - "Justice for All" IBT, Series 3; VHS (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Justice for Janitors Eyewitnesses, Series 3; VHS (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - The Kamber Group Teamsters, 1991-06-26; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - The Kamber Group "Get Out the Vote" PSA's 4 Teamsters, 1988-09-27; Series 3; VHS (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Kansas City Overnite Workers Speak Overteamster (1 of 5), Series 3; VHS (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Kansas City Overnite Workers Speak Overniteamsters (2 of 5), Series 3; VHS (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Kansas City Overnite Workers Speak Overniteamsters (3 of 5), Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Kansas City Overnite Works Speak Overniteamster (4 of 5), Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Kansas City Overnite Workers Speak Overniteamster (5 of 5), Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - King Day Rally, Atlanta, Overnite Tape 1, 2001-01-15; Series 3; betacam (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - King Day Rally, Atlanta Overnite Tape 2, 2001-01-15; Series 3; Betacam (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - "Kroger Rally" Cincinnati, 2003-06-26-2003-06-27; Series 3; VHS (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - KYW-TV Report on Trucks and "Crash" Provided by Pennsylvania Conference of Teamsters, 1991-05-08-1991-05-09; Series 3; VHS (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Labor Answers the Call Labor Institute of Public Affairs, 1995; Series 3; VHS (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Labor's Turning Point 1934 Minneapolis Teamsters Strike 45 mins, Series 3; VHS (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - L'Alena: une menace pour la securite routiere, 1996; Series 3; Video cassette (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Len Martin- Leafletting Ouside Interview with Wanda- Outside Cafeteria Food/Workers Inside Plant; Aaron and Dottie at Work- #41SF, 1985-01-29; Series 3; Video Cassette (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Interview with Len Martin #44SF, 1985-01-30; Series 3; Video cassette (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - A Line in the Sand: The Struggle at the Hotel Normandy, 1991-1992; Series 3; VHS (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - "Little City" Presentation, Series 3; VHS (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - LIUNA- Laborers:Century of Pride and Strength, Series 3; VHS (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Livelyhood-Show #1 Shift Change Embargoed until 11/21/97, 1997-11-21; Series 3; VHS (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Lo Que Usted Dice Cuenta 16 min, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Local 840 Teamsters Messenger Organizing Campaign PBS McNeil Lehrer Newshour, UPN Channel 9 News, Series 3; VHS (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Local Union "A Guide to New Members" Local 480, 2002-10-18; Series 3; Betacam (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - "Locked Out in America: Voices from Ravenswood" We Do the Work, Series 3; VHS (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - "The Long Day at Overnite" IBT -Rough Cut-, 2001-06-15; Series 3; VHS (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Lost Futures- The Problems of Child Labor American Federation of Teachers, Series 3; VHS (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Lubbock, Texas- Texas Fair Trade Caravan, 1993-05-20; Series 3; VHS (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - McNeil/Lehrer, 1977; Series 3; VHS (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Memphis, Overnite [Abuses (?)] Original, 1999-07-24; Series 3; Betacam (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - MFC/JBT Joint Sexual Harassment Training, Series 3; VHS (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - MFC/IBT Joint Sexual Harassment Training ABF Freight System, Series 3; VHS (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - MFCS Joint Sexual Harassment Training ABF Freight System, Series 3; VHS (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - MFCA/IBT Joint Sexual Harassment Training New Penn Motor Express, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - MFCA/IBT Joint Sexual Harassment Training Yellow Freight System, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Minnesota at Work "Free Trade: Who's Gonna Pay" Spring 1992, Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Tom Leedham and the Troublemakers Labor Notes Banquet Program., Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - MSNBC Coverage of Wal-mart Ad Blitz and the UFCW Response The Daily Show with Jon Stewart on Wal-mart, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - MSNBC Hardball: Hoffa-Kerry Endorsement, 2004-02-17; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Motor Freight Carrier Assn./IBT- Sexual Harassment Video, 2000-12-11; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Motor Freight Carriers/IBT Joint Sexual Harassment Training APA Transport, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - moveon.org Bushin 30 sec Spot Finalist (undated), Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - News Highlights of the Strike Against the Pittsburgh Press- Old Version, 1993-03-30; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - News Highlights of the Strike Against the Pittsburgh Press, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - News Highlights of the Strike Against the Pittsburgh Press, Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - "News Highlights of the Strike Against the Pittsburgh Press", Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - News Highlights of the Strike Against the Pittsburgh Press, 1993-02-03; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper "Teamsters Settle Strike" Detroit Coverage, 2000-12-20; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper "Detroit [Newspaper] Rally", 1999-03-28-1999-03-29; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - "A Nickel an Hour for Teamster Power", Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - No. California Teamsters Demonstration Rancho Murieta, CA, 1996-10-4; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - No. Calif. Teamster Apprenticeship Training, Unedited, 1996-10-4; Series 3; U-matic (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - NTR Rally- IBT Crew HBO Huff Project DC, 2000-04-12; Series 3; Betacam (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - "Non-Traditional Women's PSA" IBT 30sec, 1994-02-24; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - "Non-Traditional Women's PSA" IBT, 1994-02-24; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - "Non-Traditional Women's PSA" IBT 30 sec, 1994-02-24; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters/NAFTA "Ten Years of Broken Promises", 2004-06-17; Series 3; VHS (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - NAFTA/Jobs ABC World News Tonight, Washington DC, 1993-11-04; Series 3; U-Matic (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - NAFTA: Threat to Highway Safety, 1994; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - "NAFTA Threat to Highway Safety" IBT, 1995-12-28; Series 3; Betacam (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - NAFTA "Ten Years of Broken Promises", 2003-11-24; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - "NAFTA: Ten Years of Broken Promises" Teamsters/NAFTA, 2004; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - NAFTA Ten Years of Broken Promises, 2004-03-23; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - NAFTA/Mexican Trucks CBS Evening New DC, 1995-12-18; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - NBC Nightly News Pension Funds, 2004-01-09; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - New Power for Rail Labor: BMWE + Teamsters Stronger Together, 2004-08-04; Series 3; Betacam (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - New Power for Rail Labor: BMWE and Teamsters Stronger Together, Series 3; VHS Cassette (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - New Power for Rail Labor: BMWE + Teamsters Stronger Together 6min 54sec, 2004-08-04; Series 3; Betacam (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - "A New Voice for American Workers", 1995-09; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - New Teamsters UPS Visuals Original, 1992-09; Series 3; VHS cassette (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - On Target- Organizing's Audio Magazine Volume II- George Meany Center for Labor Studies, Inc., 1995; Series 3; Audio cassette (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - On the Road at Overnite w/ an intro by Willie Nelson, 1997; Series 3; VHS (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - On the Road at Overnite with an Intro with Willie Nelson, 1997; Series 3; VHS (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - One Strike and You're Out! Produced by: Committee for Workplace fairness RT 13:00, Series 3; VHS (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Organizing: Assessing Our Level of Support 15:00, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Organizing: Assessing Our Level of Support 15:00, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Organizing: Assessing Our Level of Support 15:00, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Organizing: Assessing Our Level of Support 15:00, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Organizing: Assessing Our Level of Support 15:00, 1996; Series 3; VHS (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Organizing: Teamsters Try to Unionize Fedex Workers, 2000-12-22; Series 3; VHS (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Organizing for the Future- The International Federation of Building and Wood Workers: History, Structure, Activities, Series 3; VHS (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Organizing: Teamsters Rock Las Vegas Rally- America West/Clark County Organization Tape 2 of 2, 2002-10-16; Series 3; Betacam (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - "OSHA UPS" R1+R2, 1992-03-30; Series 3; VHS (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - "OSHA UPS" R3+R4, 1992-03-30; Series 3; VHS (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - "OSHA UPS" R5+R6, 1992-03-30; Series 3; VHS (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - "OSHA UPS" R7 + R8, 1992-03-30; Series 3; VHS (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - "OSHA UPS" R8, 1992-03-30; Series 3; Betacam (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - OSHA/UPS Agreement Rough Cut IBT, 1992-07-10; Series 3; VHS (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Our Decision. Our Future., Series 3; VHS (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Out of the Shadows: A Story from the Heart of Working America, Series 3; VHS (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Out of the Shadows: A Story from the Heart of Working America, Series 3; VHS (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Out of the Shadows: A Story from the Heart of Working America, Series 3; VHS (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Out of the Shadows: A Story from the Heart of Working America, Series 3; VHS (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Out of the Shadows: A Story from the Heart of Working America, Series 3; VHS (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Outsourcing Jobs Lou Dobbs Tonight CNN, 2004-03-25; Series 3; VHS (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Overnight Abuse, Atlanta #3, 1999-07-23; Series 3; Betacam (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Overnite Teamsters: Truckers Unite Rally Louisville, Kentucky, 1995-03-11; Series 3; VHS (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Overnite Teamsters: Truckers Unite Rally Louisville, Kentucky, 1995-03-11; Series 3; VHS (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - "Overnite Transportation Strike" Headline News, Richmond, 1999-09-24; Series 3; VHS (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - "Overnite Trucking Protest" Eyewitness News and Fox 35 News Orlando, 2000-04-14; Series 3; VHS (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Overnite Trucking Protest Rally The News at Ten, 2000-03-10-2000-03-11; Series 3; VHS (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Overtime WRC-TV (NBC), 2003-07-13; Series 3; VHS (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Port Truckers Rally Tape 2, 2000-03-22; Series 3; Betacam (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Post Office Exterior Shots, Series 3; Betacam (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - "The Power of Dead-Even Rule + Other Gender Differences" Workplace Invisible Rules- Men, Women and Teams Conflict: Rules of Engagement, Series 3; VHS (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Professional Speakers Video Brochure Theodore Roosevelt AKA Keith McGough, Series 3; VHS (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Project Rise Video, Series 3; VHS (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Project Rise Video 11 min, Series 3; VHS (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - "Proud to be a Teamster" and "We're America's Teamsters", 1986; Series 3; VHS (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Proud to be a Teamster: Fred Travalena as: Ronald Reagan; Richard Nixon; John Houseman; Clint Eastwood and Willie Nelson, Series 3; VHS (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Presidential State of the Union Address, 1999-01-19; Series 3; VHS (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - "Public School Cafeterias" Inside Edition, 2003-09-10; Series 3; VHS (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Public Services Local 911 Roll 1 of 3, 2000-10-24; Series 3; Betacam (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Public Services Justice for Janitors Service Employees International Union, Series 3; VHS (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Puerto Rico Red Cross Training and Oregon Flood News Clips, Part 2, 1996-06; Series 3; Betacam (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - "People Just Like You" Glen Pearcy Production, Washington DC, Series 3; VHS (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Photos Larchmont, Paris, 1996-05-01; Series 3; DVD (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Pittsburgh Strike Window Dub Ralph Graves Productions, Inc, Series 3; VHS (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Pittsburgh Press I, Series 3; VHS (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Pittsburgh Press II, Series 3; VHS (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Pittsburgh Strike (Window Dub) 12+35, 1998-01-08; Series 3; VHS (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Pittsburgh Newspaper Strike- Erik Devereux Interviewed Teamsters: TV/NBC, Washington DC, 1992-08-01; Series 3; VHS (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Political Action "Teamsters Rally for Truckers in Dallas" Various Coverage, 2001-03-05; Series 3; VHS (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Political Action WTO/Seattle Protest "Brett Caldwell, Teamsters", 1999-11-30; Series 3; VHS (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Political Action WTO- Dave Ross Show w/ Han Shan of the Ruckus Society, 1999-11-17; Series 3; VHS (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Political Action "NAFTA Concerns" Morning Connect, 2001-02-20; Series 3; VHS (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Port Teamsters Rally Washington DC, 2000-05-22; Series 3; Betacam (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Port Teamster Rally Tape 1, 2000-03-22; Series 3; Betacam (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - "Railway Safety" CNN, 2005-01-17; Series 3; VHS (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Ready or Not Leisure: Part 1 (Education, Hobbies, Travel, Recreation) #9, Series 3; U-Matic (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Report on Methyl Bromide Teamsters CBC Evening News, DC @7pm, 1992-11-12; Series 3; VHS (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Restoring Employee Rights is Good for America, 1993; Series 3; VHS (Box 104, Folder 2)